Religious Broadcasters Interview Collection
Religious Broadcasters Interview Collection
2000-2001
S.I. Newhouse School of Public Communications
9 linear ft.
Interviews with significant or influential religious media figures including televangelists and radio and television talk show hosts. Notable names include Jim Bakker, Rabbi Boruch Shlomo Cunin, Al-Haaj Ghazi Khankan, Pat Robertson, John Spong, Elizabeth Thoman.
2534132
Biographical History
With funding from the Lilly Foundation Syracuse University undertook a project to conduct and videotape oral interviews from significant or influential religious media figures. Interviews were conducted in 2000 and 2001.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The Religious Broadcasters Interview Collection consists of 30 videotaped Interviews with religious broadcasters. Interviewees include Jim Bakker, televangelist and Assemblies of God minister; Christian musician Ralph Carmichael; Paul Crouch, co-founder and president of the Trinity Broadcasting Network (TBN); Rabbi Boruch Shlomo Cunin, director of Chabad-Lubavitch activities on the West Coast; Alberto Cutié, host of the religious talk show Padre Alberto; Rex Humbard, televangelist and host of Cathedral of Tomorrow; Pamela Ilott, director of religious broadcasting for CBS; Al-Haaj Ghazi Khankan, executive director of the Council on American Islamic Relations; Ben Kinchlow, Christian radio and television talk-show host; Pat Robertson, televangelist, founder of Christian Broadcasting Network, and host of The 700 Club; John Spong, former Bishop of Newark; and Elizabeth Thoman, founder of Media&Values magazine and the Center for Media and Values.
The collection also contains Masters (mini-DV video cassette) and Audio versions (audiocassette) for most, but not all, of the interviews. Transcripts consists of typed transcripts of most, but not all, of the interviews.
Arrangement of the Collection
U-matic, Betacam-SP, and VHS tapes of interviews are boxed in no particular order; to simplify locating a given interview the inventory below lists them in alphabetical order by interviewee. Mini-DV masters and audio versions of video interviews are labelled but loose in the box, while transcripts are foldered in alphabetical order. Formats available for a given interview vary.
Related Material
has a number of broadcast media-related collections. Please refer to for a complete listing
Subject and Genre Headings
Religion and Philosophy; Radio, television, film; Armstrong, Richard N., 1945-; Bakker, Jim, 1940-; Carmichael, Ralph, 1927-; Clarke, David E.; Cooke, Phil.; Crouch, Paul F., Sr. (Paul Franklin), 1934-2013.; Cunin, Boruch Shlomo.; Cutié Bressler, Alberto.; Fore, William F.; Humbard, Rex, 1919-2007.; Ilott, Pamela.; Khankan, Al-Haaj Ghazi Y.; Kinchlow, Ben, 1936-; McClurken, D.W.; McSweeney, Thomas J.; Moss, James, 1926-2001.; Pomeroy, David W.; Price, Nelson L.; Robertson, Pat.; Rose, Jerry K.; Schuller, Robert H. (Robert Harold), 1926-2015.; Spong, John Shelby.; Sweeney, Terrance A.; Thoman, Elizabeth, Sister.; Religious broadcasters -- United States -- Interviews.; Radio broadcasting -- Religious aspects.; Radio in religion.; Television broadcasting -- Religious aspects.; Television in religion.; Audiocassettes.; Audiotapes.; Betacam-SP.; Interviews.; Mini-DV.; Sound recordings.; Transcripts.; U-matic.; Videotapes.; VHS.
Access Restrictions
The majority of our archival and manuscript collections are housed offsite and require advanced notice for retrieval. Researchers are encouraged to contact us in advance concerning the collection material they wish to access for their research.
Acquisition Information
Generated by Syracuse University, 2000-2001.
Inventory
- Interviews
  Interviews are in a variety of video formats, including U-matic, VHS, and Betamax.
  - Armstrong, Richard N. interviewed by David Marc (tape 1 of 3), 17 May 2000; rel_broad_int_001; U-matic; running time 60:00 (Box 1)
  - Armstrong, Richard N. interviewed by David Marc (tape 2 of 3), 17 May 2000; rel_broad_int_002; U-matic; running time 60:00 (Box 1)
  - Armstrong, Richard N. interviewed by David Marc (tape 3 of 3), 17 May 2000; rel_broad_int_003; U-matic; running time 60:00 (Box 1)
  - Armstrong, Richard N. interviewed by David Marc, 17 May 2000; rel_broad_int_060; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 3)
  - Armstrong, Richard N. interviewed by David Marc (tape 1 of 2), 17 May 2000; rel_broad_int_040; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 3)
  - Armstrong, Richard N. interviewed by David Marc (tape 2 of 2), 17 May 2000; rel_broad_int_041; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 3)
  - Armstrong, Richard N., interview with Father James Keller, [no date]; rel_broad_int_104; "Gift of Richard Armstrong"; 1 inch videotape: SMPTE Type C (Box 6)
  - Bakker, Jim interviewed by David Marc, Vernon, Florida (tape 1 of 2), 12 Dec 2000; rel_broad_int_042; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 3)
  - Bakker, Jim interviewed by David Marc, Vernon, Florida (tape 2 of 2), 12 Dec 2000; rel_broad_int_043; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 3)
  - Bakker, Jim interviewed by David Marc, Vernon, Florida, 12 Dec 2000; rel_broad_int_061; label has misspelled name "Jim Baker"; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 3)
  - Bane, Will, United Methodist Communications, interviewed by David Marc, Nashville, TN, original (tape 1 of 5), 24 Oct 2000; rel_broad_int_011; interview transcript not available; Betacam: SP; running time 30:00 (Box 1)
  - Bane, Will, United Methodist Communications, interviewed by David Marc, Nashville, TN, original (tape 2 of 5), 24 Oct 2000; rel_broad_int_012; interview transcript not available; Betacam: SP; running time 30:00 (Box 1)
  - Bane, Will, United Methodist Communications, interviewed by David Marc, Nashville, TN, original (tape 3 of 5), 24 Oct 2000; rel_broad_int_013; interview transcript not available; Betacam: SP; running time 30:00 (Box 1)
  - Bane, Will, United Methodist Communications, interviewed by David Marc, Nashville, TN, original (tape 4 of 5), 24 Oct 2000; rel_broad_int_014; interview transcript not available; Betacam: SP; running time 30:00 (Box 1)
  - Bane, Will, United Methodist Communications, interviewed by David Marc, Nashville, TN, original (tape 5 of 5), 24 Oct 2000; rel_broad_int_015; interview transcript not available; Betacam: SP; running time 30:00 (Box 1)
  - Bane, Will, United Methodist Communications, interviewed by David Marc, Nashville, Tennessee (tape 1 of 2), 24 Oct 2000; rel_broad_int_044; interview has no transcript; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 3)
  - Bane, Will, United Methodist Communications, interviewed by David Marc, Nashville, Tennessee (tape 2 of 2), 24 Oct 2000; rel_broad_int_045; interview has no transcript; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 3)
  - Bane, Will interviewed by David Marc, 24 Oct 2000; rel_broad_int_062; interview has no transcript; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 3)
  - Carmichael, Ralph interviewed by Stephen O'Leary, [no date]; rel_broad_int_063; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 3)
  - Carmichael, Ralph interviewed by Stephen O'Leary (tape 1 of 2), [no date]; rel_broad_int_046; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 3)
  - Carmichael, Ralph interviewed by Stephen O'Leary (tape 2 of 2), [no date]; rel_broad_int_047; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 3)
  - Clarke, David E., Ph.D. interviewed by David Marc (tape 1 of 2), 26 Jun 2000; rel_broad_int_004; label has misspelled name "David Clark"; U-matic; running time 60:00 (Box 1)
  - Clarke, David E., Ph.D. interviewed by David Marc (tape 2 of 2), 26 Jun 2000; rel_broad_int_005; label has misspelled name "David Clark"; U-matic; running time 60:00 (Box 1)
  - Clarke, David E., Ph.D. interviewed by David Marc (tape 1 of 1), 26 Jun 2000; rel_broad_int_048; label has misspelled name "David Clark"; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 3)
  - Cooke, Phil interviewed by David Marc, Burbank, California (tape 2 of 2), 7 Aug 2000; rel_broad_int_049; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 3)
  - Cooke, Phil interviewed by David Marc, Burbank, California (tape 1 of 2), 7 Aug 2000; rel_broad_int_050; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 3)
  - Cooke, Phil interviewed by David Marc, 7 Aug 2000; rel_broad_int_064; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 3)
  - Crouch, Paul F., Sr. interviewed by Stephen O'Leary in Tustin, California (tape 1 of 2), 8 Jul 2000; rel_broad_int_006; U-matic; running time 60:00 (Box 1)
  - Crouch, Paul F., Sr. interviewed by Stephen O'Leary in Tustin, California (tape 2 of 2), 8 Jul 2000; rel_broad_int_007; U-matic; running time 60:00 (Box 1)
  - Crouch, Paul F., Sr. interviewed by Stephen O'Leary, Tustin, California (tape 1 of 1), 8 Jul 2000; rel_broad_int_051; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 3)
  - Crouch, Paul F., Sr., [no date]; rel_broad_int_052; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 3)
  - Cunin, Baruch Shlomo, Rabbi interviewed by Michael Epstein, Los Angeles, California (tape 1 of 2), 13 Dec 2000; rel_broad_int_053; label has misspelled name "Rabbi Boruch Shlomo Cunin"; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 3)
  - Cunin, Baruch Shlomo, Rabbi interviewed by Michael Epstein, Los Angeles, California (tape 2 of 2), 13 Dec 2000; rel_broad_int_054; label has misspelled name "Rabbi Boruch Shlomo Cunin"; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 3)
  - Cunin, Baruch Shlomo, Rabbi interviewed by Michael Epstein, 13 Dec 2000; rel_broad_int_065; label has misspelled name "Rabbi Boruch Shlomo Cunin"; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 3)
  - Cutié, Alberto, Father [Albert], Rector of St. Benedict's Church, interviewed by Mort Silverstein, Miami Beach, FL (tape 1 of 2), 17 Jan 2000; rel_broad_int_024; U-matic; running time 60:00 (Box 2)
    Additional credits: Silverstein, Mort, producer; Marc, David, series producer; "Religious Broadcasting in America" Center for the Study of Popular Television.
  - Cutié, Alberto, Father [Albert], Rector of St. Benedict's Church, interviewed by Mort Silverstein, Miami Beach, FL (tape 2 of 2), 17 Jan 2000; rel_broad_int_025; U-matic; running time 60:00 (Box 2)
  - Cutié, Alberto, Father [Albert], Rector of St. Benedict's Church interviewed by Mort Silverstein, Miami Beach, Florida (tape 1 of 1), 17 Jan 2000; rel_broad_int_055; interview has transcript; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 3)
  - Ferm, Lois, Dr., Coordinator at the Billy Graham Library, interviewed by David Marc (tape 1 of 3), 11 May 2000; rel_broad_int_008; U-matic; running time 60:00 (Box 1)
  - Ferm, Lois, Dr., Coordinator at the Billy Graham Library, interviewed by David Marc (tape 2 of 3), 11 May 2000; rel_broad_int_009; U-matic; running time 60:00 (Box 1)
  - Ferm, Lois, Dr., Coordinator at the Billy Graham Library, interviewed by David Marc (tape 3 of 3), 11 May 2000; rel_broad_int_010; U-matic; running time 60:00 (Box 1)
  - Ferm, Lois, Dr., Coordinator at the Billy Graham Library, interviewed by David Marc (tape 1 of 2), 11 May 2000; rel_broad_int_056; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 3)
  - Ferm, Lois, Dr., Coordinator at the Billy Graham Library, interviewed by David Marc (tape 2 of 2), 11 May 2000; rel_broad_int_057; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 3)
  - Ferm, Lois, Dr., Coordinator at the Billy Graham Library, interviewed by David Marc, 11 May 2000; rel_broad_int_066; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 3)
  - Fore, William F., Rev., Director of the Broadcasting and Film Commission of the National Council of Churches, interviewed by David Marc, California (tape 1 of 2), 8 Aug 2000; rel_broad_int_058; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 3)
  - Fore, William F., Rev., Director of the Broadcasting and Film Commission of the National Council of Churches, interviewed by David Marc, California (tape 2 of 2), 8 Aug 2000; rel_broad_int_059; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 3)
  - Fore, William F., Rev., Director of the Broadcasting and Film Commission of the National Council of Churches, interviewed by David Marc, 8 Aug 2000; rel_broad_int_067; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 3)
  - Goodman, Jane interviewed by David Marc, Canyon Lake, TX, Tape 1 (tape 1 of 3), 17 Mar 2000; rel_broad_int_026; U-matic; running time 60:00 (Box 2)
  - Goodman, Jane interviewed by David Marc, Canyon Lake, TX, Tape 2 (tape 2 of 3), 17 Mar 2000; rel_broad_int_027; U-matic; running time 60:00 (Box 2)
  - Goodman, Jane interviewed by David Marc, Canyon Lake, TX, Tape 2 cont. (tape 3 of 3), 17 Mar 2000; rel_broad_int_028; U-matic; running time 30:00 (Box 2)
  - Goodman, Jane interviewed by David Marc, 17 Mar 2000; rel_broad_int_068; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 3)
  - Goodman, Jane interviewed by David Marc, Canyon Lake, Texas (tape 1 of 2), 17 Mar 2000; rel_broad_int_072; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 5)
  - Goodman, Jane interviewed by David Marc, Canyon Lake, Texas (tape 2 of 2), 17 Mar 2000; rel_broad_int_073; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 5)
  - Humbard, Rex, Reverend, interviewed by David Marc, Pigeon Forge, TN, master (Tape 1 of 5), 29 Aug 2000; rel_broad_int_016; Betacam: SP; running time 30:00 (Box 1)
  - Humbard, Rex, Reverend, interviewed by David Marc, Pigeon Forge, TN, master (tape 2 of 5), 29 Aug 2000; rel_broad_int_017; Betacam: SP; running time 30:00 (Box 1)
  - Humbard, Rex, Reverend, interviewed by David Marc, Pigeon Forge, TN, master (tape 3 of 5), 29 Aug 2000; rel_broad_int_018; Betacam: SP; running time 30:00 (Box 1)
  - Humbard, Rex, Reverend, interviewed by David Marc, Pigeon Forge, TN, master (tape 4 of 5), 29 Aug 2000; rel_broad_int_019; Betacam: SP; running time 30:00 (Box 1)
  - Humbard, Rex, Reverend, interviewed by David Marc, Pigeon Forge, TN, master (tape 5 of 5), 29 Aug 2000; rel_broad_int_020; Betacam: SP; running time 30:00 (Box 1)
  - Humbard, Rex, Reverend, interviewed by David Marc, 29 Aug 2000; rel_broad_int_069; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 3)
  - Humbard, Rex, Reverend interviewed by David Marc, Pigeon Forge, Tennessee (tape 1 of 2), 29 Aug 2000; rel_broad_int_074; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 5)
  - Humbard, Rex, Reverend interviewed by David Marc, Pigeon Forge, Tennessee (tape 2 of 2), 29 Aug 2000; rel_broad_int_075; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 5)
  - Ilott, Pamela interviewed by David Marc, Canyon Lake, TX (tape 1 of 3), 17 Mar 2000; rel_broad_int_029; U-matic; running time 60:00 (Box 2)
  - Ilott, Pamela interviewed by David Marc, Canyon Lake, TX (tape 2 of 3), 17 Mar 2000; rel_broad_int_030; U-matic; running time 60:00 (Box 2)
  - Ilott, Pamela interviewed by David Marc, Canyon Lake, TX (tape 3 of 3), 17 Mar 2000; rel_broad_int_031; U-matic; running time 60:00 (Box 2)
  - Ilott, Pamela interviewed by David Marc, 17 Mar 2000; rel_broad_int_070; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 3)
  - Ilott, Pamela interviewed by David Marc, Canyon Lake, Texas (tape 1 of 2), 17 Mar 2000; rel_broad_int_076; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 5)
  - Ilott, Pamela interviewed by David Marc, Canyon Lake, Texas (tape 2 of 2), 17 Mar 2000; rel_broad_int_077; case labeled "tape 2 of 2"; tape labeled "tape 1 of 2"; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 5)
  - Khankan, Al-Haaj Ghazi Y., executive director of Council on American-Islamic Relations and Director of interfaith affairs at the Islamic Center of Long Island, NY, interviewed by Morton Silverstein, 1 Dec 2000; rel_broad_int_071; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 3)
  - Khankan, Al-Haaj Ghazi Y., executive director of Council on American-Islamic Relations and Director of interfaith affairs at the Islamic Center of Long Island, NY interviewed by Mort Silverstein, Islamic Center of Long Island (tape 1 of 2), 1 Dec 2000; rel_broad_int_078; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 5)
  - Khankan, Al-Haaj Ghazi Y., executive director of Council on American-Islamic Relations and Director of interfaith affairs at the Islamic Center of Long Island, NY interviewed by Mort Silverstein, Islamic Center of Long Island (tape 2 of 2), 1 Dec 2000; rel_broad_int_079; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 5)
  - Kinchlow, Ben, Reverend, interviewed by David Marc (tape 1 of 2), 15 Feb 2000; rel_broad_int_032; U-matic; running time 60:00 (Box 2)
  - Kinchlow, Ben, Reverend, interviewed by David Marc (tape 2 of 2), 15 Feb 2000; rel_broad_int_033; U-matic; running time 60:00 (Box 2)
  - Kinchlow, Ben, Reverend, interviewed by David Marc, 15 Feb 2000; rel_broad_int_080; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 5)
  - McClurken, D. W. (Bill), Reverend interviewed by David Marc (tape 1 of 2), 30 Mar 2001; rel_broad_int_081; handwritten on tape and case: "part 1 & 3"; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 5)
  - McClurken, D. W. (Bill), Reverend interviewed by David Marc (tape 2 of 2), 30 Mar 2001; rel_broad_int_082; handwritten on tape and case: "part 2"; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 5)
  - McSweeney, Thomas, Monsignor, interviewed by David Marc, The Christopher's Building, NYC (tape 1 of 3), 31 Mar 2000; rel_broad_int_034; U-matic; running time 60:00 (Box 2)
  - McSweeney, Thomas, Monsignor, interviewed by David Marc, The Christopher's Building, NYC (tape 2 of 3), 31 Mar 2000; rel_broad_int_035; U-matic; running time 60:00 (Box 2)
  - McSweeney, Thomas, Monsignor, interviewed by David Marc, The Christopher's Building, NYC (tape 3 of 3), 31 Mar 2000; rel_broad_int_036; U-matic; running time 60:00 (Box 2)
  - McSweeney, Thomas, Monsignor, interviewed by David Marc, The Christopher's Building, NYC (tape 1 of 2), 31 Mar 2000; rel_broad_int_083; label has misspelled name "Monsignor Thomas McSweeny"; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 5)
  - McSweeney, Thomas, Monsignor, interviewed by David Marc, The Christopher's Building, NYC (tape 2 of 2), 31 Mar 2000; rel_broad_int_084; label has misspelled name "Monsignor Thomas McSweeny"; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 5)
  - Moss, Jim, Dr., interviewed by David Marc, Pigeon Forge, Tennessee (tape 1 of 2), 16 Feb 2001; rel_broad_int_085; interview has no transcript; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 5)
  - Moss, Jim, Dr., interviewed by David Marc, Pigeon Forge, Tennessee (tape 2 of 2), 16 Feb 2001; rel_broad_int_086; interview has no transcript; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 5)
  - Moss, Jim, Dr. interview by David Marc, Studios of Gospel Network Television, Pigeon Forge, Tennessee (tape 1 of 3), 16 Feb 2001; rel_broad_int_105; interview has no transcript; Betacam: SP; running time 60:00 (Box 6)
  - Moss, Jim, Dr. interview by David Marc, Studios of Gospel Network Television, Pigeon Forge, Tennessee (tape 2 of 3), 16 Feb 2001; rel_broad_int_106; interview has no transcript; Betacam: SP; running time 60:00 (Box 6)
  - Moss, Jim, Dr. interview by David Marc, Studios of Gospel Network Television, Pigeon Forge, Tennessee (tape 3 of 3), 16 Feb 2001; rel_broad_int_107; interview has no transcript; Betacam: SP; running time 60:00 (Box 6)
  - Moss, Jim, Dr., interviewed by David Marc, 16 Feb 2001; rel_broad_int_101; interview has no transcript; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 5)
  - Pomeroy, David, Reverend, interviewed by David Marc, Spring Valley, New York (tape 1 of 2), 30 Mar 2001; rel_broad_int_087; interview has no transcript; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 5)
  - Pomeroy, David, Reverend, interviewed by David Marc, Spring Valley, New York (tape 2 of 2), 30 Mar 2001; rel_broad_int_088; interview has no transcript; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 5)
  - Pomeroy / Eden, 3-1-89; rel_broad_int_089; interview has no transcript; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 5)
  - Price, Nelson, Pastor, interviewed by David Marc (tape 1 of 3), 15 Jun 2000; rel_broad_int_037; mismatching date on label reads "6/11/2000"; U-matic; running time 60:00 (Box 2)
  - Price, Nelson, Pastor, interviewed by David Marc (tape 2 of 3), 15 Jun 2000; rel_broad_int_038; mismatching date on label reads "6/11/2000"; U-matic; running time 60:00 (Box 2)
  - Price, Nelson, Pastor, interviewed by David Marc (tape 3 of 3), 15 Jun 2000; rel_broad_int_039; mismatching date on label reads "6/11/2000"; U-matic; running time 60:00 (Box 2)
  - Price, Nelson, Pastor, interviewed by David Marc (tape 1 of 2), 15 Jun 2000; rel_broad_int_090; mismatching date on label reads "6/11/2000"; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 5)
  - Price, Nelson, Pastor, interviewed by David Marc (tape 2 of 2), 15 Jun 2000; rel_broad_int_091; mismatching date on label reads "6/11/2000"; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 5)
  - Price, Nelson, Pastor, interviewed by David Marc, 15 Jun 2000; rel_broad_int_100; mismatching date on label reads "6/11/2000"; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 5)
  - Robertson, Pat "Marion Gordon", Christian Broadcasting Network, interviewed by David Marc (uncorrected), 16 Feb 2000; rel_broad_int_092; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 5)
  - Robertson, Pat "Marion Gordon", Christian Broadcasting Network, interviewed by David Marc (corrected), 16 Feb 2000; rel_broad_int_093; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 5)
  - Robertson, Pat "Marion Gordon" interview by David Marc (tape 1 of 2), [no date]; rel_broad_int_113; Betacam: SP; running time 60:00 (Box 6)
  - Robertson, Pat "Marion Gordon" interview by David Marc (tape 2 of 2), [no date]; rel_broad_int_114; Betacam: SP; running time 45:00 (Box 6)
  - Robertson, Pat "Marion Gordon" interview by David Marc, Christian Broadcasting Network (tape 1 of 2), 16 Feb 2000; rel_broad_int_115; U-matic; running time 60:00 (Box 6)
  - Robertson, Pat "Marion Gordon" interview by David Marc, Christian Broadcasting Network (tape 2 of 2), 16 Feb 2000; rel_broad_int_116; U-matic; running time 60:00 (Box 6)
  - Rose, Jerry, Total Living Network, interviewed by David Marc, Chicago, Illinois (tape 1 of 2), 9 Nov 2000; rel_broad_int_094; interview has no transcript; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 5)
  - Rose, Jerry, Total Living Network, interviewed by David Marc, Chicago, Illinois (tape 2 of 2), 9 Nov 2000; rel_broad_int_095; interview has no transcript; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 5)
  - Rose, Jerry, Total Living Network, interview by David Marc, Chicago, Ilinois (tape 1 of 5), 9 Nov 2000; rel_broad_int_108; interview has no transcript; Betacam: SP; running time 30:00 (Box 6)
  - Rose, Jerry, Total Living Network, interview by David Marc, Chicago, Ilinois (tape 2 of 5), 9 Nov 2000; rel_broad_int_109; interview has no transcript; Betacam: SP; running time 30:00 (Box 6)
  - Rose, Jerry, Total Living Network, interview by David Marc, Chicago, Ilinois (tape 3 of 5), 9 Nov 2000; rel_broad_int_110; interview has no transcript; Betacam: SP; running time 30:00 (Box 6)
  - Rose, Jerry, Total Living Network, interview by David Marc, Chicago, Ilinois (tape 4 of 5), 9 Nov 2000; rel_broad_int_111; interview has no transcript; Betacam: SP; running time 30:00 (Box 6)
  - Rose, Jerry, Total Living Network, interview by David Marc, Chicago, Ilinois (tape 5 of 5), 9 Nov 2000; rel_broad_int_112; interview has no transcript; Betacam: SP; running time 30:00 (Box 6)
  - Schuller, Robert H., Dr. interviewed by Dr. Michael Epstein, original (tape 1 of 3), 4 Oct 2000; rel_broad_int_021; Betacam: SP; running time 30:00 (Box 1)
  - Schuller, Robert H., Dr. interviewed by Dr. Michael Epstein, original (tape 2 of 3), 4 Oct 2000; rel_broad_int_022; Betacam: SP; running time 30:00 (Box 1)
  - Schuller, Robert H., Dr. interviewed by Dr. Michael Epstein, original (tape 3 of 3), 4 Oct 2000; rel_broad_int_023; Betacam: SP; running time 30:00 (Box 1)
  - Schuller, Robert H., Dr. interviewed by Dr. Michael Epstein, 4 Oct 2000; rel_broad_int_096; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 5)
  - Schuller, Robert H., Dr., interviewed by Dr. Michael Epstein, 4 Oct 2000; rel_broad_int_102; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 5)
  - Spong, John, Bishop, interviewed by David Marc, Morristown, New Jersey (tape 1 of 2), 11 Sep 2000; rel_broad_int_097; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 5)
  - Spong, John, Bishop, interviewed by David Marc, Morristown, New Jersey (tape 2 of 2), 11 Sep 2000; rel_broad_int_098; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 5)
  - Stevens, Betty and Paul, Dr., interviewed by Dr. David Clark, Southern Baptist Communication Center, Fort Worth, Texas, 26 Jun 2000; rel_broad_int_099; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 5)
  - Stevens, Betty and Paul, Dr., interviewed by Dr. David Clark, 26 Jun 2000; rel_broad_int_103; VHS; running time 120:00 (Box 5)